fxgm.com 2012-03-01

# Privacy Policy

                                             Privacy Policy
FXGM respects each individual's right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take great
pride in maintaining the privacy and therefore the loyalty of each individual client, by providing the required
security. The provisions of this notice apply to former as well as current customers.
1. Personal Information
In order to provide you with the very best service, when you apply to become a FXGM customer or open a
live account, we will ask you for personal information. This information will assist us in evaluating your
financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, keeping you informed about products and
services that may be of interest to you, and providing you with a better customer experience.
2. Required Information May Include:
Application Information - full name, address, birth date, identity social security number, occupation, assets,
and income.
Transaction Information - Information about your transactions with us and/or our affiliates, records of past
communications. These may include: your account balances, trading activity, past inquiries and our
responses.
Verification Information – This may be required to verify your identity, and may include passport or drivers
license.
Note: Anti-Money Laundering ("AML") regulations and the USA Patriot Act requires financial institutions to
collect information and take action, where necessary to verify a customer’s identity.
Note: FXGM does not intentionally collect information from persons under thirteen years of age.
3. The Use of Cookies
We use a technology called "cookies", which enables us to provide you a better experience in using our
website by sending small text files from our servers to your computer. These cookies do not track your
private information.
4. Sharing Information:
a. General Policy
FXGM do not disclose your personal information to third parties, except as described in this Policy. Third
party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform support
services for your account or facilitate your transactions with FXGM, including those that provide
professional, legal, or accounting services to FXGM. Non-affiliate companies that assist FXGM in providing
services are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it and to
use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes
dictated by FXGM.
FXGM may also disclose a customer’s personal information to a third party in order to fulfill their
instructions or pursuant to express consent. It is important to us that you know that FXGM will not sell your
personal information.

b. Regulators
FXGM may disclose your personal information to third parties as permitted by, or in order to comply with,
applicable laws and regulations. This may include disclosing personal information in order to cooperate
with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies, as may be necessary to protect our rights or
property.
5. Failure to Provide Personal Information
You have a choice to supply any or all of the personal information required. However, missing information
may result in our being unable to open or maintain your account and /or to provide you with our services.
6. Opt Out
Should you choose to have your name and personal data removed from our database, you can do so by
sending an email to cs@fxgm.eu
7. Amendments
Any amendments to our privacy policy that affect the personal information of users collected on our website
will be notified to the users, within a reasonable time, via email. Users will have a choice whether or not we
use the information in a different manner. Any amendments made by us that do not affect personal
information will be posted on our website.
8. Contact Information
Whether you wish to talk to us about our privacy policy or any other issue, the professional team at FXGM
is available to assist you 24/7; please feel free to contact us via e-mail, postal address, phone and fax or
use our chat facility to IM a customer service representative.
Address:
FX Global Market (FXGM) Ltd
69, Makarios Avenue
Tlais Tower, 5th Floor
1070 Nicosia, Cyprus
• Fax: +357 22 766 333
• Tel: +357 22 460 260
• E-mail: cscs@fxgm.eu
This Privacy Policy is in effect from May, 2009.
